http://www.apax.com/privacy-statement/

Apax Digital
Apax Global Alpha
InvestorsInside ApaxCompanyHistoryFundsGovernance & complianceValuesApproachPeopleInvestorsReportsApax thought leadershipPortfolio company reportsApproachProcessSectorsTech & TelcoServicesHealthcareConsumerPracticesDigital ExpertiseCapital MarketsOperational ExcellenceInvestmentsTech & TelcoServicesHealthcareConsumerAll investmentsResponsibilitySustainabilitySustainable investmentPortfolio monitoringApax Sustainability CommitteeApax India CSRApax FoundationSocial mobility and social entrepreneurshipApax staff 'matching' schemeSocial investmentsImpetus - The Private Equity FoundationNewsPress releasesApax in the newsMedia kitVideo library
Search
View print basket (  ) Follow usShare this pagePrint this pageAdd to print basket
Print basket
Apax Partners LLP Privacy Statement
Apax and data privacy
Apax Partners LLP, each General Partner of the funds advised by Apax Partners LLP (the “Apax Funds”) and each of their respective affiliates (collectively, solely for the purpose of this Privacy Statement, "Apax" or “we” or “us” or “our”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This privacy statement sets out the basis on which we will process any personal information that we may collect about you as a visitor to any Apax related website (including www.apax.com and www.apax.us.com) or to the premises of any Apax entity, or any contact at any Apax related investor, potential investor, customer, supplier or other business partner.
The information that we collect about you
We may collect and process the following information about you:
Information that you provide: This is information about you that you provide by filling in forms on an Apax website (or any other form you provide Apax), providing a business card (or similar), while attending an Apax related event or corresponding with Apax by telephone, post, email or otherwise. It may include, for example, your name, address, email address and telephone number; information about your business relationship with Apax; information about your professional role, background and interests; and information relating to events.
Information that our websites and other systems collect about you:
If you visit our websites they will automatically collect some information about you and your visit, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your device to the Internet and some other information such as your browser type and version and the pages on the sites that you visit.
Our websites may also download "cookies" to your device – this is described in our separate cookie statement.
If you exchange emails, telephone conversations or other electronic communications with our employees and other staff members, our information technology systems will record details of those conversations, sometimes including their content.
Some of our premises have closed circuit TV systems which may record you if you visit our premises, for security and safety purposes.
Other information: We may also collect some information from other sources. For example:
If we have a business relationship with the organisation that you represent, your colleagues or other business contacts may give us information about you such as your contact details or details of your role in the relationship.
We sometimes collect information from third party data providers or publicly available sources for anti-money-laundering, background checking and similar purposes, and to protect our business and comply with our legal and regulatory obligations.
The uses that we make of your information
We may use your information for particular purposes including the following:
to operate, manage, develop and promote our business and, in particular, our relationship with you or the organisation you represent (if any) and related transactions;
to send you emails containing marketing information which we believe you will find relevant and interesting;
to operate, administer and improve our websites and premises and other aspects of the way in which we conduct our operations;
to protect the security of our premises;
to protect our business from fraud, money-laundering, breach of confidence, theft of proprietary materials and other financial or business crimes; and
to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations and bring and defend legal claims.
We may from time to time review information about you held in our systems – including the contents of and other information related to your email and other communications with us – for compliance and business-protection purposes as described above. This may include reviews for the purposes of disclosure of information relevant to litigation and/or reviews of records relevant to internal or external regulatory or criminal investigations. To the extent permitted by applicable law these reviews are intended to be conducted in a reasonable and proportionate way and where appropriate will be approved at an appropriate level of management. They may ultimately involve disclosure of your information to governmental agencies and litigation counterparties as described below. Your emails and other communications may also occasionally be accessed by persons other than the member of staff with whom they are exchanged for ordinary business management purposes (for example, where necessary when a staff member is out of the office or has left Apax).
We will generally only process your personal information as necessary so that we can pursue the purposes described above, and then only where we are not aware that our processing does not prejudice you or your privacy in a way that would override our legitimate interest in pursuing those purposes. In exceptional circumstances we may also be required by law to disclose or otherwise process your personal information. We will tell you, when we ask you to provide information about yourself, if provision of the requested information is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation or, on the other hand, if it is purely voluntary and there will be no implications if you decline to provide the information. Otherwise you should assume that we need the information for our business or compliance purposes (as described above). If you are uncertain as to Apax's need for information that we request from you, please contact the Apax representative asking for the information, or Contact us (see below), with your query.
Disclosure and international transfer of your information
We may disclose personal information about you, where reasonably necessary for the various purposes set out above, including:
to other Apax entities;
to your colleagues within the organisation that you represent;
to service providers who host our websites or other information technology systems or otherwise hold or process your information on our behalf, under strict conditions of confidentiality and security;
to partners who run any events that you sign up to through our websites;
to a person who acquires any business and assets that previously had any such information, or relevant parts of them; or
in exceptional circumstances:
to competent regulatory, prosecuting and other governmental agencies, or litigation counterparties, in any country or territory;  or
where we are required by law to disclose.
These disclosures may involve transferring your personal information overseas. If you are dealing with us within the European Economic Area (or the UK, after it has left the European Economic Area), you should be aware that this may include transfers to countries outside the European Economic Area / UK, which do not have similarly strict data privacy laws. In those cases, where we transfer personal data to other members of the Apax group or our service providers, we will aim to ensure that our arrangements with them are governed by data transfer agreements, designed to ensure that your personal information is protected, on terms approved for this purpose by the European Commission. Please Contact us (see below) if you would like to know whether any such agreements are in place or, if so, to see a copy.
Retention and deletion of your information
We will delete the information that we hold about you when we no longer need it. Specific information about our record retention policies is available on request. Please Contact us (see below).
Note that we may retain some limited information about you even when we know that you have left the organisation that you represent, so that we can maintain a continuous relationship with you if and when we are in contact with you again, representing a different organisation.
Your rights
You may have a right of access to the personal information that we hold about you, and to some related information, under data protection law. You can also require any inaccurate personal information to be corrected or deleted. You can object to our use of your personal information for direct marketing purposes at any time and you may have the right to object to our processing of some or all of your personal information (and require them to be deleted) in some other circumstances.
If you wish to exercise any of these rights, please Contact us as set out below. You can also lodge a complaint about our processing of your personal information with the office of the UK Information Commissioner (www.ico.gov.uk).
Contact us
We welcome questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy statement and our processing of personal information. Please email dataprotection@apax.com.
Changes to this policy
Any changes we make to this privacy statement in the future will be posted to our websites (at www.apax.com and www.apax.us.com) and also available if you Contact us. Please check back frequently to see any changes.
Contact usUS PersonsPrivacy statementCookie NoticeTerms & conditionsUK Slavery ActAccessibilitySitemapApax Partners
© 2020 Apax Partners
Search
